<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="unavailable">Sorry this currency info is not available</string>

    <string name="btc">Bitcoin (Symbol: BTC) is a global digital currency and peer-to-peer payment system designed by an unknown programmer,
        or a group of programmers called Satoshi Nakamoto. It was issued as open-source software network in 2009.
        The interface is a digital system and transactions which are verified by network nodes and recorded in a peer-to-peer blockchain network,
        occur between customers directly without an intermediary.</string>

    <string name="eth">Ethereum (Symbol: ETH) is a free-source, unrestricted-blockchain decentralized computing platform which allows smart contract (scripting) functions.
        Built in late 2013 by a digital token researcher and developer, Vitalik Buterin, this coin became published on 30 July 2015. It supplies a decentralized
        Turing-complete digital machine, the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), which can run scripts by applying a global network of public nodes.
        Ethereum also provides a virtual token called ether, which can be shifted between accounts and used to return member nodes for their accomplished computations.</string>

    <string name="ltc">Litecoin (Symbol: LTC) is an open source-based digital currency operating accordingly to the MIT/X11 license.
        Litecoin creation and transfer is based on a public source protocol of code and centered around the community-driven feature. A
        lthough Litecoin shares some same technical elements with Bitcoin (BTC), it features some methodological improvements over Bitcoin
        and many other digital coins. Two significant enhancements are the implementation of Segregated Witness and adoption of Lightning Network.
        These upgrades facilitate a higher number of trades through a system with a particular time frame, lowering likely bottlenecks which are often seen in Bitcoin system.</string>

    <string name="xrp">Designed in 2012, Ripple (Symbol: XRP) is a blockchain system uses real-time gross settlement system to transfer and exchange money.
        The coin has the Ripple Transaction Protocol (RTXP) or Ripple protocol designed on a scattered open-source Internet protocol,
        consensus ledger, and XRP coin. Ripple attempt to promote safe, immediate and nearly free global monetary transactions with every size.
        Ripple helps tokens represent real money, digital currency, commodity or any other intrinsic value items like the number of phone minutes.
        Ripple is relied on a shared, public ledger employing a consensus process that allows payments, exchanges, and remittance in an allocated process.</string>

</resources>